Yi-Hsiu Lee



+81-80-4447-9968 / +886-913-272-282



s30401s@gmail.com



Kanazawa, Japan

PROFILE

1 year's experience in front-end development with React.js framework.

5 years' experience in field of blockchain investment.

Currently a graduate student in computer science / Information Security Lab., Kanazawa University and NCCU.

Research topic is about decentralized identity on blockchain. Also interesting in every new thing developed on blockchain.

SKILLS

JavaScript / React.js / RWD HTML / CSS Python / Django Ethereum / Solidity

Language TOEIC: 780

AWARDS

NFTHack 2022 - Filecoin leadership board

Project Name: NFT Starter

Description: A tool for project owners to start their NFT sales in minutes, without concerning about development.

Url:

https://ethglobal.com/showcase/nft-starter-jsu6d

EDUCATION

Master of Electrical Engineering and Computer Science

Kanazawa University, Japan. Information Security Lab. 2021 -

Master of Computer Science

National Chengchi University, Taiwan. Information Security Lab. 2020 -

Research topic: Blockchain-based Self-sovereign Identity System with Attribute-based Issuance

- Split the power of identity attributes' issuance and revocation.
- Returned the authority of management to users and met the requirements of GDPR.

Bachelor of Information Management

National Taiwan University of Science and Technology, Taiwan 2016 - 2020

Senior High School

National Wu-Ling Senior High School, Taiwan. 2013 - 2016

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Freelancer

Taiwan / 2021.06 -

- Developed a customized transaction flow (n-to-1).
- Used REST API, WebSocket for Connecting Binance and FTX API.
- Based on React.js framework.

Front End Developer (Intern)

APTAN INC. / Taiwan / 2020.03 - 2020.09

- Developed user interface and management interface for projects.
- Connected API and organizing data for display.
- Based on React.js, React Native, Angular.
- Development Projects: Taischool (Taiwan), Clothestelling App. (Taiwan), HugPea (China)

Front End Developer (Intern)

Cimforce Ltd. / Taiwan / 2018.07 - 2018.09

• Developed user interface and webAPI based on Angular framework.